Winter was starting.
From last spring to fall...
I lost half a year's worth of memories.
I heard that I got into a car accident.
But I can't even remember that.
This past month...
the same old days continued.
Yo, Haru.
What's wrong?
Spacing out like that.
How do you manage here? It's freezing.
Something is wrong.
Wrong?
During this past month...
I...
Something keeps bothering me.
Something important?
I can't remember... no matter how hard I try.
Actually....
Keisuke, you said it before, right?
I was in the Gardening Club before.
Right, right, the Gardening Club.
Why did I join the Gardening Club?
U-Um...
It seems that Kisaragi-sensei recommended it to you.
That's what Sensei said.
T-Tsuwabuki-kun.
When your body gets better, come back to the Gardening Club whenever you can.
Y-Yeah.
Um... Akihime, was it?
Yeah, that's right!
Akihime Sumomo!
It was the Gardening Club.
Sumomo.
Are you okay?
You're not pushing yourself, right?
It's okay, I'm fine.
Let's go, Nako-chan. We'll be late for the afternoon class.
The properties of a metal.
First, malleability.
The property of being able to be flattened out into thin sheets.
Second, ductility.
It means the ability of the matter to be stretched long and thin, and to have a special metallic luster.
Also, the amount of heat and electricity that can be transferred...
Haru-kun...
His body seems healthy.
That's a relief.
I'm happy every day...
because the memories are scattered out in many places.
Every day, I can see Haru-kun.
Hey, Haru, you're free after this, right?
I am, but...
Well then...
I'm happy.
What is it?
Let's go somewhere.
See you again tomorrow, Haru-kun.
Again...
I get anxious whenever sunset comes around.
What is this feeling?
I'm anxious about something.
Something as I see the sunset...
What is this?
Today, for the first time, I dated Haru-kun.
That day was just like a dream.
Even when we rode the boat, I thought about the kiss...
Then Haru-kun looked at me, and smiled brightly.
I was looking at the stars.
They looked as if they were about to fall...
And there was someone beside me...
Sumomo!
kizuite hora kira kira hikaru hoshi kuzu no youni
Please notice just like the light from the stardust
No.
I promised...
G-Good morning.
Ah, um...
Is this the Gardening Club?
Yeah.
Um...
Why is Tsuwabuki-kun, on a Sunday...
I was thinking that maybe I'll remember something.
I... What was I doing in the Gardening Club?
You were...
pulling out weeds and watering flowers.
We even did things like planting acorns.
Acorns?
Like this.
Also...
There was a time when you made the sprinkler.
Tsuwabuki-kun did a really good-
I'm okay.
It's nothing, so I'm fine.
Hang on a second.
Let's see, a handkerchief...
Why do I have...?
Um...
Hold out your finger.
T-Tsuwabuki-kun.
Would you like to see the greenhouse?
You might remember something.
The flowers are very pretty.
At night, it's like a planetarium.
There are lots of stars...
Planetarium?
Sorry, there's somewhere I need to go to right now.
See you later.
You're as clumsy as usual.
Aspalas-san.
Thank you.
It's a medicine I made with the star drops I've collected.
Medicine? How...
The star drops that are important to Aspalas-san...
It's all right.
Anyways, if you let Tsuwabuki-kun drink this, he will regain his memory of loving you.
I just know it.
That's the most important thing right now, isn't it?
Thank you.
I knew it all along...
...that Nona-chan was a nice person.
I knew it a long time ago.
But you know, I'll be okay without the medicine.
Why?!
We promised.
Haru-kun will definitely keep the promise.
Until then, I'll keep waiting.
But, that is...
I don't know what the promise was,
but he forgot everything, you know!
For Nona-chan's feelings, I'm happy.
I'll keep it as a precious charm.
Even from now on, you'll be my friend, right?
You-...
You're stupid...
You're too nice.
I didn't want to lose to that child.
Being the daughter of a genius...
Because of that, she was overflowing with talent.
It was unforgivable.
But, I understand now...
...the reason why I lost to that child.
What I was lacking wasn't talent.
It was that kindness.
We'll always be friends, Nona-chan!
The Planetarium.
I was probably here before.
I was with someone.
We were walking together.
Who...
That person was always with me.
Haru-kun.
Why do I long for something?
That girl definitely...
rode on this merry-go-round.
Kind...
Cute...
I loved that girl.
I definitely did.
Keisuke, tell me.
If you know who that girl is, right now...
In that moment, I realized...
that I've typed this name countless times.
Yeah, that's right!
Akihime Sumomo!
Akihime.
Akihime Sumomo.
Would you like to see the greenhouse?
This song...
Haru-kun's pocket...
It was a magical pocket.
The memory of us secretly hidden...
It's also hiding in my heart.
Star-sama...
The planetarium...
And the merry-go-round.
They are all held there.
Our treasures...
Haru-kun.
Sumomo!
I've definitely called Akihime by Sumomo.
Always by my side...
Sumomo.
The acorn that was a stray...
It finally bloomed.
Together... Together we planted it...
Haru-kun.
Sumomo...
I love you.
What has happened, I don't remember.
Not even one bit.
But my heart remembers.
I love Sumomo.
Haru-kun.
I don't know when I started loving you.
So I, about Sumomo...
I'll love you once again...
from the very beginning.
For example,
when looking at the stars outside the window...
when writing in the secret journal about the day...
Mysterious things suddenly fall down from the sky.
The key to everything are the star drops that fall down from the night sky, and...
a special girl.
It is a magical story of, "A seven colored first love that encompasses you."